{
  "status": "success",
  "data": [
    {
      "question": "To adjust or fit to the condition",
      "answer": "Adapt",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": ["Adapt", "Adopt", "Adept", "Amiable"]
    },
    {
      "question": "To take a child of other parents legally",
      "answer": "Adopt ",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": ["Adopt ", "Adapt", "Adept", "Amiable"]
    },
    {
      "question": "well skilled",
      "answer": "Adept",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": ["Adept", "Adapt", "Adopt", "Amiable"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Lovable",
      "answer": "Amiable",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": ["Amiable", "Adapt", "Adopt", "Amicable"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Friendly",
      "answer": "Amicable",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": ["Amicable", "Adapt", "adopt", "Amiable"]
    },
    {
      "question": "By the side ",
      "answer": "Beside",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": ["Beside", "Besides", "Beneficient", "Benificial"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Additionally",
      "answer": "Besides",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": ["Besides", "Beside", "Benificial", "Beneficient"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Kind",
      "answer": "Beneficient",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": ["Beneficient", "Besides", "Benificial", "Beside"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Useful",
      "answer": "Benificial",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": ["Benificial", "Beneficient", "Besides", "Beside"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Silly",
      "answer": "Childish",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": ["Childish", "child like", "Disease", "decease"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Innocent",
      "answer": "child like",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": ["child like", "decease", "Childish", "Disease"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Sickness",
      "answer": "Disease",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": ["Disease", "Childish", "child like", "decease"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Death",
      "answer": "decease",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": ["decease", "Disease", "Childish", "child like"]
    },
    {
      "question": "To war",
      "answer": "Martial",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": ["Martial", "Marital", "Stationary", "Stationery"]
    },
    {
      "question": "To marriage",
      "answer": "Marital",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": ["Marital", "Martial", "Stationery", "Stationary"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Fixed",
      "answer": "Stationary",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": ["Stationary", "Marital", "Martial", "Stationery"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Materials like pen,ink etc",
      "answer": "Stationery",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": ["Stationery", "Martial", "Marital", "Stationary"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Natural ability",
      "answer": "Flair",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": ["Flair", "Flare", "Compliment", "Complement"]
    },
    {
      "question": "To burn brightly",
      "answer": "Flare",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": ["Flare", "Flair", "Complement", "Compliment"]
    },
    {
      "question": "A remark",
      "answer": "Compliment",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": ["Compliment", "Flare", "Flair", "Complement"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Completely",
      "answer": "Complement",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": ["Complement", "Flair", "Flare", "Compliment"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Calm",
      "answer": "Quiet",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": ["Quiet", "Quite", "Further", "Farther"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Completely",
      "answer": "Quite",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": ["Quite", "Quiet", "Farther", "Further"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Additional",
      "answer": "Further",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": ["Further", "Quite", "Quiet", "Farther"]
    },
    {
      "question": "More distance",
      "answer": "Farther",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": ["Farther", "Further", "Quite", "Quiet"]
    },
    {
      "question": "A personal record",
      "answer": "Diary",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": ["Diary", "Dairy", "Dual", "Duel"]
    },
    {
      "question": "A farm where milk is processed",
      "answer": "Dairy",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": ["Dairy", "Diary", "Duel", "Dual"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Double",
      "answer": "Dual",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": ["Dual", "Duel", "Dairy", "Diary"]
    },
    {
      "question": "A fight between two person",
      "answer": "Duel",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": ["Duel", "Diary", "Dual", "Dairy"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Campaign",
      "answer": "Canvass",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": ["Canvass", "Dual", "Duel", "Canvas"]
    },
    {
      "question": "A cloth used for  drawing and making tents",
      "answer": "Canvas",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": ["Canvas", "Canvass", "Diary", "Duel"]
    },
    {
      "question": "She proved herself very..........at playing chess",
      "answer": "Adept",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": ["Adept", "Adopt", "Adapt", "inept"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Doctors could ------- the problem easily.",
      "answer": "Identify",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": ["Identify", "Identification", "Identicate", "Identificate"]
    },
    {
      "question": "They neglected the teacher's --------------",
      "answer": "Advice",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": ["Advice", "Advise", "Advize", "Advaise"]
    },
    {
      "question": "The superstar plays a ----------- role in the film.",
      "answer": "Dual",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": ["Dual", "Duel", "Duet", "Dubious"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Kerala is blessed with ----------- vegetation",
      "answer": "Laxuriant",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": ["Laxuriant", "Laxurious", "Lustrous", "Industrious"]
    },
    {
      "question": "His words had no ----- on the employees",
      "answer": "Effect",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": ["Effect", "Effective", "Affective", "Affect"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Reena has ---------- for painting.",
      "answer": "Flair",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": ["Flair", "Fair", "Flare", "Fare"]
    },
    {
      "question": "He was ------------ red handed.",
      "answer": "Caught",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": ["Caught", "Quote", "Cot", "NOT"]
    },
    {
      "question": "He gets up early everyday--------- sunday",
      "answer": "Except",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": ["Except", "Exempt", "Accept", "Except"]
    },
    {
      "question": "He is the--------- this estate.",
      "answer": "Heir",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": ["Heir", "Hair", "Hire", "Hare"]
    }
  ]
}
